嗨  你俩在干什么
Hey, you guys. Hey, what are you doing?
筹备婚礼
Figuring out our wedding plans.
太巧了  我们也正合计这事呢
Funny. We were doing the same thing.
疯了  场地  服装  食品
It's really crazy. The hall, the dress, the food.
没想到结个婚这么贵
I had no idea how expensive this was.
是很贵
Yeah, it is really pricey.
第一次算出结婚费用  我被那个数字吓呆了
I freaked when I heard the numbers.
结果你们怎么做的
So, what did you two do about it?
简单
It was simple.
我想出了一些省钱方案
I came up with some cost-cutting solutions...
列了个清单  结果莫妮卡叫我去死
...wrote out a list, and Monica told me to go to hell.
没钱好省的
There's no way around it.
只能接受现实  确实会花很多钱
Just accept that this is gonna cost a lot of money.
听说每年花在结婚上的钱高达400亿
I heard that weddings are, like, a $40 billion-a-year industry.
这其中我贡献过半
Yeah. And I'm responsible for just, like, half of that.
我觉得这钱应该用在更有意义的事上
But really, it does seem like this money could be put to better use.
当真
Are you serious?
把婚礼经费
Yeah. How would you feel
捐献给慈善事业
if we gave all the wedding money to charity...
我们就到市政厅登个记  如何
...and we just got married at City Hall?
这让我越发想娶你了
I think it would make me wanna marry you even more.
不得不说  你们的高姿态  很好
I gotta say, you guys, that's an incredible gesture.
下次你结婚也这么干如何
Maybe you do that next time you get married.
不不不  下次我要在夏威夷斜阳下结婚
No, no, no. The next time's gonna be Hawaii at sunset.
不过下下次可以听取你的意见
But maybe the time after that.
-嘿  忙啥呢  -嘿
- Hey. What's going on? - Hey.
领养中心有人来家访
Our adoption social worker is coming,
所以我们在扫除
so we're cleaning the apartment.
我们
"We"?
你不想我掺和
You know you don't want me to help.
别现在又说这个
You can't have it both ways.
这个人能决定
Is this the person who decides
你们是否收养一个孩子
whether or not you get a baby?
差不多  这人来视察我们的生活环境
Kind of. She's coming by to interview us and see where we live.
我们必须表现得完美
And it has to go perfectly,
若她对我们有丝毫不满
because if she doesn't like something about us
她就会让我们进不了
she can keep us off
全国任何一个领养的名单里
every adoption list in the state.
我可以过来友情协力一把
Hey, maybe I should stop by.
她没准爱看肥皂剧
She could be a soap opera fan.
小人物认识演艺名流
It's very impressive
可以蓬壁生辉呢
when the little people know a celebrity.
小人物
"Little people"?
名流
"Celebrity."
我觉得我做的差不多了
So I think I'm just about done here.
除非你还在哪
Unless you have any bad stuff hidden somewhere,
藏了像黄书  香烟什么的
like porn or cigarettes?
什么
What?
-才没有  -钱德勒
- No. - Chandler.
我没有
I don't,
这样玷污人家清白太气人了
and I'm offended by the insinuation.
沙发下没有杂志
So there's not a magazine under the couch...
厕所水箱后没有一包香烟
...or cigarettes taped to the back of the toilet tank...
录象机里没有A片
...or a filthy video in the VCR?
香烟和杂志我认帐
I'll admit to the cigarettes and magazine.
但带子不是我的
But that tape is not mine.
也不是我的
It isn't mine.
我想我们永远不会知道是谁的了
I guess we'll never know whose it is.
可以帮忙吗
May I help you?
我们来给孩子们
Yes. We're here
捐一大笔钱
to make a rather sizable donation to the children.
捐钱不论多少  心意都是一样重
Any contribution, large or small,
我们都会感激
is appreciated.
数目这样大
I think you're gonna appreciate
你一定会把屎都感动出来了
the crap out of this one.
你们真大方
Well, this is very generous.
我们要匿名捐助
And we don't want any recognition.
完全匿名
This is completely anonymous.
完全匿名  就写两个陌生人
Completely anonymous. From two kind strangers.
先生甲和菲比·布菲
Mr. X and Phoebe Buffay.
如果你们愿意
Well if you like,
我们可以把二位的名字登到新闻通讯里
we can include your names in our newsletter.
没必要
Not necessary.
布菲的拼法是  B-U-F-F-A-Y
Buffay is spelled B-U-F-F-A-Y.
先生甲的写法是  迈克·汉尼根
And X is spelled "Mike Hannigan."
我代表孩子们多谢两位
Well, on behalf of the children, thank you both very much.
我很高兴我们这么做了  感觉真棒
I'm glad we did this. It feels so good.
是啊  非常棒
It does. It feels really good.
还有免费T恤拿
Oh, look. And we get these free T-shirts.
那是我健身穿的
Actually, that's the shirt I wore to the gym.
难怪是湿的
It's moist.
艾玛会很快起床的
Hi. Emma will be up in a minute.
好啊
Oh, good.
嘿  罗斯  听说你跟查莉的事了
Hey, Ross, listen. I heard about you and Charlie.
替你难过
I'm really sorry.
没事
That's okay.
美貌的考古学家多的是
I'm sure there are tons of other beautiful paleontologists out there.
当然
Absolutely.
只有一个  就是她
There was one. She's it.
其他的就好象是桥洞居民一样
All the rest look like they should live under a bridge.
今天想怎么玩
So, what are you gonna do today?
带艾玛去街心游乐场怎么样
I was thinking of taking Emma to the playground.
天啊  什么
Oh, my God. What?
我又没说
Like I said, I was thinking of
带她去武器弹药博物馆
taking Emma to the Museum of Knives and Fire.
听着  罗斯
Okay, look, Ross.
我反对艾玛去游乐场
I do not want Emma going to the playground.
因为
Because...?
好吧  如果你想知道…
All right, if you must know, I had a traumatic...
我小时候荡秋千遇险
...swing incident when I was little.
-真的  -我才四岁
- Seriously? - Yes. I was 4 years old.
我荡秋千
And I was on the swing...
突然头发缠到铁链上
...and then all of a sudden my hair got tangled in the chain.
结果老妈剪掉我一大缕头发
And to get me out,
才救我出来
my mom had to cut a big chunk of my hair.
结果有好几星期头发才长齐
And it was uneven for weeks.
你竟熬了过来
And you made it through that?
简直可以拍成电影
I wonder who's gonna play you in the movie.
你尽管拿我取笑
Okay, fine, you can make fun of me.
反正我就是不想艾玛去
I do not want Emma going there.
我在想能不能让克莱尔·丹妮丝扮演我
And I was thinking Claire Danes.
你的悲剧令我同情
Look, I'm sorry to hear about your tragedy.
不过秋千很安全
But the swings are perfectly safe.
而且艾玛喜欢荡秋千
And besides, Emma loves them.
我们同去  你就知道了
You should come, and you'll see.
秋千速度高达40英里/小时
Those things go, like, 40 miles an hour.
当你荡到最高处
And there's that moment when you're at the top...
鬼才知道会不会返回地球
...when you just don't know if you're gonna return back to Earth.
宇宙充满小孩子绕轨道运行
Space is filled with orbiting children.
求你了  来嘛
Look, please, just come on.
你若看见艾玛的小表情
When you see the look on Emma's face,
决不会后悔
I swear, you won't regret it.
-好吧  -太好了
- All right. - Good.
你不会像有的妈妈那样
You don't wanna be a mom
把自己失去理智的恐惧遗传给小孩吧
who passes her irrational fears to her children.
"失去理智"
"Irrational," huh?
下次你被家里的蜘蛛吓到
I'll remember that next time
我们再谈这个话题
you freak out about a spider in your apartment.
这两个可以相提并论吗  秋千上
That's the same. I'm sure there are 30
有30种不同毒液
different species of poisonous swings.
天啊  领养中心的来早了
Oh, my God. The adoption lady is early.
好的好的  镇静镇静
Okay. Okay. Here we go. Here we go.
站直咯
Stand up straight.
微笑
Big smile.
你们好  请问这是"毛骨悚然"家吗
Hello. Is this the Creepy residence?
还以为是领养中心的来了
We're waiting for the adoption lady.
你来得正好
But I'm glad you're here.
今早打扫时发现的
I was cleaning this morning
不知道你用不用得上
and I found this.
我不知道你是不是想用  但是...
I don't know if you wanna use it, but....
你真好
Oh, this is so sweet of you.
但是你知道吗
But you know what?
我并不需要这头纱
I won't be needing a veil,
我实际上都不会穿婚纱
I actually won't be wearing a dress at all!
我告诉过你
I told you,
裸体婚礼我不会参加的
I am not coming to a naked wedding!
我们不会招待宴请
No. We're not having a big reception.
我们把婚礼经费
we took the money we were gonna spend on a wedding
捐给儿童慈善事业了
and we donate them to the children charity.
你真疯狂
That's crazy!
抱歉  只是无法想象
I'm sorry. I can't imagine giving up
一生只有一次啊
my one wedding day like that.
我们不同
Well, we're different.
我不在乎什么盛大婚礼
I don't care about having a huge party.
头纱你戴是很美  但是...
This is really nice for you, but....
你看我一戴上  简直就...
Oh, please. I put this on and I just look like--
美极了
Well, radiant.
管它呢
All right, but who cares?
我不需要头纱婚纱这些玩意
I don't need a pretty veil and a fancy dress.
对  你们是互许终身
That's right. You're making a commitment.
不管在广场举行还是别的什么地方都是一样
You know, that's the same whether you do it at the Plaza or....
-你选了啥地方  -市政厅
- Where you gonna do it? - City Hall.
好地方
Oh, that sounds nice.
我刚去过那做评审委员
I was just there for jury duty.
他们把那打理得非常整洁漂亮呢
They've really spruced that place up.
没关系...
Okay. It's okay...
我已经下定决心
I've made my decision.
但我真正想要的是一个盛大的婚礼
What I really want is a great big wedding.
但钱已经捐啦
But you gave all the money to charity.
可以要回来
Well, I'll just ask for it back.
不行吧
I don't think you can do that.
怎么不行
Why not?
她这可是结婚
This is her wedding day.
这可比什么愚蠢的小孩子重要多了
That's way more important than some stupid kids.
说得好  亲爱的
That's sweet, honey,
但这些话省下来说给领养中心的人听吧
but save something for the adoption lady.
-好  小心点  -好
- All right, okay. Be careful. - Okay.
小心  小心她头发
Careful. Watch her hair. Watch her hair!
她才三根毛
Rach, she's got, like, three hairs.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
但是很漂亮
But they're just so beautiful.
糟糕  扯掉一根
Oh, my God, I just pulled one out.
我保证  她很安全
I promise you she's safe.
你看她多喜欢玩秋千
Watch how much she loves this.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
你准备好了吗  亲爱的  开始喽
Are you ready, sweetie? Here we go.
小心
Okay, careful. Okay.
她笑了
She's smiling.
看  她真的很喜欢
Look at that, she does like it.
看到没  我告诉过你的吧
See, I told you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
看看她真有不怕死的精神
Look at her, she's a little daredevil.
让我推好不好
Oh, God. Let me push. Can I push?
哦  当然
Oh, absolutely.
你去拿相机
Oh, God. Okay, get the camera.
在尿布包里
It's in the diaper bag.
好
Okay.
还怕秋千
See? Scared of the swings.
现在觉得傻了吧
I bet you feel pretty silly.
我们真要把钱要回来
We're asking for the money back?
结婚要用
It's for our wedding day.
这小子喜欢男的女的
Now, is this guy gay or straight?
我们非得出美人计
Because one of us has to start flirting.
你们一天来捐两次钱
You here to make another donation the same day?
真是前所未有呢
I don't think that's ever happened before.
同性恋  你上
Gay. Go.
天呐  你的衬衣好帅
Oh, my God, I love your shirt.
我们今天捐的钱
The donation we made earlier?
我们想要回来
Well, we want it back.
什么
Excuse me?
那是办婚礼的钱
Okay, that money was for a big wedding
我们本来不想大办
we thought we didn't want.
但现在我们改变了主意
But it turns out we do.
所以你要我们退还
So you're asking us
你们捐给孩子们的钱
to refund your donation to the children?
对
Yeah.
这样感觉真不错
This feels really good.
对不起  真的
I'm sorry. I am.
但婚礼对我相当重要
But this wedding's just really important to me.
不关我事
Hey, it's none of my business.
也许这是件好事
Besides, this is probably a good thing.
别把孩子惯坏了
We've really been spoiling the children,
让他们吃饱穿暖干嘛
what with all the food and warm clothing.
你这么说不公平
That's not fair.
结婚是大事
A person's wedding is important.
尤其对于我来说
And especially to me.
我没参加过毕业典礼
I didn't have a graduation party.
没有毕业舞会
And I didn't go to prom.
在我的16岁生日的时候
And I spent my sweet 16 being chased around a tire yard...
我被精神病人在一个废旧轮胎场地狂追
...by an escaped mental patient
他还说
who, in his own words, wanted to:
杀我什么的
"Kill me, or whatever."
我应当有个隆重的婚礼
So I deserve a real celebration.
我不会让你个流汗男
And I'm not gonna let some sweaty little man
弄的我觉得内疚
make me feel badly about it.
她也有可能是在说我
She could've been talking about either one of us.
我是劳拉
Hi, I'm Laura.
我来做领养家访
I'm here for your adoption interview.
我是莫妮卡  这是钱德勒
Hi, I'm Monica. And this is Chandler.
-请进  -谢谢
- Please come in. - Thank you.
请进  喝点什么
Would you like something to drink?
喝水可以了
Water would be fine.
你总算来了
We're so glad that you're here.
我们好兴奋  终于开始领养小孩的流程了
We're excited about getting this process started.
因为我们爱小孩  爱得要死
Because we love kids. Love them to death.
不是真的要孩子"死"
Well, not actually to death.
只是这么形容一下
That's just a figure of speech.
我们爱孩子  恰当合理
We love kids the appropriate amount...
符合法律法规
...as allowed by law.
-你们家好可爱  -谢谢
- Your place is just lovely. - Thank you.
这栋楼的确看起来很卫生
Yes, this building does have a wholesome,
给人家的感觉
family feel to it.
我好像来过这里
I feel like I've been here before.
这里还有谁家在申请领养吗
Any other couples in the building adopting?
是不是一楼那家
Is that that couple on the first floor?
我们应该比他们先得到孩子
Because we should get a baby before them.
他还想卖毒品给我
That guy tried to sell me drugs.
但其他人都好
But other than that,
这是栋干净卫生的楼
wholesome, wholesome building.
怎么
What?
我想起来了为什么我对这楼有记忆了
I realized why I remember this place.
真的  怎么回事
Really? What is it?
哦  没什么
Oh, it's nothing.
我和住在这栋楼里的一个男人约会
I went on a date with a guy who lived in this building.
结果无疾而终
It didn't end very well.
那人该不是叫乔伊·崔比安尼吧
That wouldn't, by any chance, be Joey Tribbiani?
-就是他  -当然是他
- Yes! - Of course it was.
良宵过后
We had a great night.
他说他再打电话给我
In the morning, he promised he'd call
结果再没联络
and he didn't.
真他妈混蛋
Rat bastard!
你们该不是他朋友
So you're not friends with him?
当然不是  不
Oh, God, no.
No, no, no.
当然不是
No. Nope.
不...
No...
抱歉提到这事
Well, I'm sorry I brought it up.
那么你们当中有人打算待在家里吗
So are either one of you planning on staying at home?
有人吗  名人驾到
Hello? Anybody in there order a celebrity?
怎么了
What was that?
过道上乱跑的疯子
That's just some crazy guy who roams the halls here.
不过他对小孩很慈祥
He's great with kids, though.
罗斯  天啊  你还好
Ross. Oh, my God, are you okay?
他妹的
Son of a bitch!
别紧张  我又没说F打头那个字
Oh, relax. I didn't say the F-word.
罗斯  看吧
Ross, see,
早告诉你了  秋千太邪恶了
I told you! Those swings are evil!
就这一次了
That is it.
这辈子再也不许
That's the last time Emma is getting on
艾玛接近它
one of those things for her entire life.
别这样  不是秋千的错
No, no, no. Okay, it wasn't the swing's fault.
是我错
It was my fault.
还有那孩子的错
And kind of that kid's fault.
他还笑呢  算你恨
Who is still laughing. Nice.
在再有人受伤之前
Come on. Can we just get out of here
我们走吧
before somebody else gets hurt?
不  等等  这样吧
No. Wait. Ok, ok. I have an idea.
你去荡秋千
I want you to get on the swing...
你会发现没什么好担心的
...and you'll see that there's nothing to be afraid of.
我知道你意欲何为了
I know what this is all about.
你一贯嫉妒我满头秀发
You've always been jealous of my hair.
这只是想你已经成年了
I just think you're an adult, okay?
该克服那些愚蠢的恐惧了
And you should get over your silly fears.
好  上就上
All right, fine. I'll do it.
好
Good.
如果你敢抓蜘蛛
If you hold a spider.
在哪儿  在哪儿
Where?! Where?!
我说"如果"你敢抓蜘蛛
If you hold a spider.
我听见了
I know.
伙计们  没事吧
Guys, is everything okay?
是我  乔伊
It's me, Joey.
领养
Adoption!
到底怎么回事
What's going on?
就是那个叫波特疯子
Oh, it's just like I said, that crazy...
在过道上跑
...Bert, roaming the halls.
伙计们
Guys?
接着跑吧  波特
Keep on roaming, Bert!
今天我们不看你疯了
We don't want any crazy today!
到底怎么了
What's going on?
我们等会再说  波特  一切都好
We'll talk later! Bert. Everything's fine!
听起来就是有问题
Everything doesn't sound fine.
他独自一个在外面  不会出事吧
Is he all right out there by himself?
没事  他有监管人
Oh, yeah. He has a caretaker.
是他哥
His older brother...
叫欧尼
...Ernie.
波特和欧尼
Bert and Ernie?
无巧不成书
You can't make this stuff up.
你没说过你16岁生日时
You never told me about that guy
被男人追杀的故事
and your sweet 16.
真可怜
I'm sorry about that.
结局还算好
Oh, it ended okay.
我朋友毙了他
One of my friends shot him.
至少你会有个体面婚礼
At least you'll get a proper wedding.
你该得的
You really deserve that.
是的  没错
Yeah, I really do.
知道吗  长这么大我还没风光过
You know, I had nothing growing up.
就像被我剥夺金钱的那些孩子一样
Just like the kids I took the money from.
不...  看出你苗头了
No... I see where this is going.
别又想让我退回去
Don't make me go back there.
我不能用这钱办婚事
Look, I can't have a wedding with this money now.
这样就有污点了
It's tainted.
好吧  退回就是了
Fine, we'll give the money back.
如果慈善捐助处那家伙
If that guy at the charity
又叫咱们难看
gives us a hard time...
我朋友的老枪好久没见过血了
...my friend hasn't shot anyone in a really long time.
我想说  这种环境
I must say this seems like
培养小孩似乎很理想
a lovely environment to raise a child in.
你尽可以在各种家具
You are welcome to look under
下面搜查
any of the furniture...
相信我
...because, believe me,
绝无黄书和香烟什么的
you won't find any porn or cigarettes under there.
在到处看看之前
Before we look around,
让我先检查下我的表
let me make sure
是不是都填好了
I have everything I need up to here.
我带你去看看婴儿房
Why don't I show you the baby's room.
你干啥
What are you doing?
你不让我进来
You wouldn't let me in.
我以为你们出事了
I thought you were in trouble.
才没有
Well, we're not.
但你叫我"波特"
But you called me "Bert."
那是"危险"的暗号
That's our code word for danger.
我们没约定过什么暗号
We don't have a code word.
没有吗
We don't?
应该约一个
We really should.
从今往后
From now on,
"波特"就用来作为遇到危险的暗号
"Bert" will be our code word for danger.
参观完婴儿房
So that was the baby's room.
下面参观哪里
What room should we see next?
除了沙发后面都可以参观
Any room that isn't behind this couch.
有些人不懂他的笑话
Some people don't get him,
但我觉得他真幽默
but I think he's really funny.
我不在乎被你粗暴对待
I did not care for that.
你得回避
You have to leave.
你和这个社工睡过
You slept with our social worker
再没联络她
and never called her back.
她还在生你的气
She is still pissed,
不能让她见到你
so she can't see you.
好  好
Okay, okay.
-怎么了  -忘了拿球棒
- What? - I forgot my bat.
天呐
Oh, my God.
最后一次告诉你
And for the last time,
我们不想和你做朋友
we do not want to be friends with you!
也不想买你的球棒
And we don't wanna buy your bat!
你来这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
"波特"...
Bert...
你们是朋友
Are you friends with him?
我来解释
I can explain.
乔伊你说
Joey?
好吧
All right. Okay.
你还敢回来  太有种了
You have got some nerve coming back here.
真不敢相信你竟从来没给我打过电话
I can't believe you never called me.
你说什么呢
Excuse me?
你可能连我名字也忘了吧
You probably don't even remember my name.
告诉你  我叫乔伊
It's Joey, by the way.
不必说你的名字
And don't bother telling me yours,
我记得  女士
because I totally remember it, lady.
我一直等你电话
I waited weeks for you to call me.
我给你电话号码了
I gave you my number.
你没联系我啊
You never called me.
还想把屎盆子往我身上扣
Don't try to turn this around on me.
我可不是
I am not some kind of social work...
让你可以随便做的
...that you can just...
社会工作
...do.
我确信给过你电话
I'm pretty sure I gave you my number.
真的吗  那你想想看
Really? Think about it. Come on.
你这么漂亮
You're a beautiful woman.
聪明又有趣
Smart, funny.
你我春风一度
We had a really good time.
如果我有你电话
If I had your number,
怎么可能不打给你
why wouldn't I call you?
就是不知道呀
I don't know.
可能我搞错了
Well, maybe I'm wrong.
对不起
I'm sorry.
现在道歉太晚啦
Hey, too late for apologies. Okay?
你伤了我的心
You broke my heart.
你知道就为了忘掉你
You know how many women
我睡了多少女人吗
I had to sleep with to get over you?
-乔伊  留步... -不
- Joey, wait-- - No!
我等得够久
I waited a long time!
不可能再等了
I can't wait anymore.
抱歉让你们笑话了
I'm sorry that you had to see that.
太丢人了
I'm so embarrassed.
没事
Oh, that's really okay.
我们理解
Yeah. We totally understand.
约会可够人受的
Dating is hard.
你们真是好人
Boy, you people are nice.
我得说…
And I've got to say...
你们一定会是很棒的父母
...l think you're going to make excellent parents.
劳拉
Laura!
我们回来啦
We're back.
你们是想再多要点钱
Are you here to take more money?
你们应该找提款机
Because I think what you're looking for is an ATM.
不不  我们把钱退给你们
No, no, we're here to give the money back.
因为你知道
Yeah. Because you know what?
一切都是为了孩子
It's all about the children.
当然  我们的婚礼也很重要
Although it's also about the wedding.
好吧  给
All right, here.
不要  天呐
No. Oh, God.
我好像还没有说
If I haven't said so already,
恭喜你啊  先生
sir, congratulations.
够了  好吗
Enough, all right?
我要插手做决定了
I'm stepping in and putting my foot down.
作为你的未来老公
As your future husband,
我说了算
I'm gonna make this decision for us.
你说咋办
What do you think we should do?
现在不是你们说了算了
You know what. It's not your decision anymore.
什么
What?
我代表纽约儿童
On behalf of the children of New York,
拒绝你们的捐款
I reject your money.
但是我们在给你钱啊
But we're giving you this.
现在退给你们
And I'm giving it back to you.
拿着吧  当作礼金好了
Come on. Consider it a contribution.
你可真够大方啊
Well, this is very generous.
支票拿走
Please take the check.
祝婚礼成功
Have a great wedding
幸福甜蜜
and a wonderful life together.
听来不错
Sounds good to me.
我们以后存了钱
We can save up, come back in a few years...
过两年捐更多
...and make an even bigger donation.
当然  下次记得找布莱恩捐
Absolutely. And when you do, make sure you ask for Brian.
-布莱恩是你  -不
- Oh, is that you? - No.
喂
Hello?
哦  嗨
Oh, hi.
天啊  真的吗
Oh, my God, really?
我迫不及待想告诉钱德勒了
I can't wait to tell Chandler.
好  再见
Okay. Goodbye.
打错电话的
Wrong number?
是劳拉
That was Laura.
她替我们大大美言
She gave us a great report
我们正式上了领养排队名单
and we're officially on the waiting list.
太好了
That's great.
我们现在就等人
Now we just wait for a call...
给我们打电话告诉我们
...and someone tells us
有个小孩等我们去领养了
there's a baby waiting for us.
喂
Hello?
看见乔伊的球棒吗
Have you seen Joey's bat?
好了  我捉到了蜘蛛
Okay. I got a spider.
有两只  我挑了只大的
There were two, I picked the bigger one.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
感觉一切正常
This feels perfectly normal.
好了  你上秋千去
Okay, get on the swing.
好啊
Okay.
好
好啊
Okay.
看到了吗
See?
啊  没事了  我可以玩秋千了
All right. I can do this.
是啊  干得好
There you go. Good for you.
知道吗  我已经习惯这小家伙了
You know what? I'm getting used to this little guy.
我已经完全感觉不到它的存在了
I don't even feel him in here anymore.
因为它爬到你脖子上去了
That's because he's on your neck.